[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
ScaledBorderAndShadow: Yes
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial Unicode MS,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Banner2,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Banner,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Place3,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Place2,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Place,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Title,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Title2,Arial Unicode MS,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Info,Arial Unicode MS,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OPch,Arial Unicode MS,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OPch2,Arial Unicode MS,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: EDch,Arial Unicode MS,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.36,0:00:28.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柯里斯迪阿諾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.98,0:00:30.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都幹掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.03,0:00:33.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三個男人 一個女人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.90,0:00:34.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.99,0:00:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四個男人 一個女人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.21,0:00:44.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就四人了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.50,0:00:46.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再清點一次屍體
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.67,0:00:49.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在就過來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.26,0:00:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波拉克一家都解決了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.89,0:01:01.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 你工作完成得真乾淨俐落
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.35,0:01:04.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待你日後的表現
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.77,0:01:06.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你的厚愛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.15,0:01:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約翰．頓 撤退了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.77,0:01:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是肯戒酒 我出雙倍酬勞也沒所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.11,0:01:18.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有這個不行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.25,0:01:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波拉克那傢伙 什麼時候弄了這樣的機關
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.08,0:03:18.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還活著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.20,0:03:19.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.96,0:03:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是波拉克的兒子嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.17,0:03:27.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.42,0:03:29.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備怎麼處理
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.67,0:03:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放著不管嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.59,0:03:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他帶回去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.51,0:03:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把我的車開過來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.98,0:03:46.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快上來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.78,0:03:56.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.58,0:03:59.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.96,0:04:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雷西歐 皮諾曹現在在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.72,0:04:19.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和預期一樣 在福蘭卡小姐的葡萄園待命中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.01,0:04:21.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.72,0:04:23.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.06,0:04:28.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 不用介意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.12,0:04:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 皮諾 你在那裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.70,0:04:44.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事啊 多梅尼柯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.71,0:04:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多該回去了 午飯的時間到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.67,0:04:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.01,0:04:57.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才過了幾個月 你就很有農夫的樣子了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.97,0:04:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.55,0:05:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有種植葡萄的才能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.02,0:05:07.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從來沒想過這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.15,0:05:12.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還年青 應該什麼都去嘗試一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.11,0:05:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮諾 今天早上也去田裡了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.99,0:05:23.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.91,0:05:27.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 福蘭克在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.87,0:05:29.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在福蘭卡的房間吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.88,0:05:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人是不是小姐的男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.96,0:05:35.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不覺得他們的關係不尋常嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.55,0:05:36.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.67,0:05:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然看起來很陰沉 但是個好男人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.97,0:05:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 你有女朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.93,0:05:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對女孩子不拿手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.69,0:05:49.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣計算就完成了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.90,0:05:52.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本該是柯里斯迪阿諾準備炸藥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.19,0:05:54.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但顯然延誤了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.03,0:05:57.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然他說是軍隊的運輸車流被攔截了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.57,0:05:58.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不知道有沒有影響
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.36,0:06:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說前段時間米蘭派的武器提供網被政府破壞了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.49,0:06:06.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來要在此地久留了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.16,0:06:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮諾曹也成長了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.63,0:06:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為這樣對他有好處
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.34,0:06:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也這樣認為嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.26,0:06:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.68,0:06:28.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定大家能在這裡忘卻紛爭與仇恨 就這樣一直生活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.44,0:06:34.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子的身心其實還是個孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.61,0:06:38.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他被孤立的感情能在這裡慢慢融化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.95,0:06:42.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得這樣下去肯定能使他有所變化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.78,0:06:46.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我已經不再能改變了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.25,0:06:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認為我是在逞強嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.50,0:06:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘗試去改變也屬於勇氣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.21,0:06:55.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逞強也沒什麼不好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.30,0:06:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣 我都會陪伴著你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.76,0:07:01.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.81,0:07:15.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起去散步一會兒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.90,0:07:25.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到能在離羅馬這麼近的地方躲起來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.66,0:07:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果連一個警察都沒追過來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.96,0:07:36.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當局只要一聽到五共和國派 就只會往北方找
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.71,0:07:40.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該能在這裡待上一段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.05,0:07:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過膩了這裡的生活嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.93,0:07:50.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.64,0:07:55.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外地習慣這兒的生活 我自己也很吃驚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.81,0:07:58.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你所想 這種生活確實不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.86,0:08:03.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多梅尼柯和帕歐拉 也常教我種植的技巧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.95,0:08:09.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這會使我身手生疏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.96,0:08:14.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,動了情就會變軟弱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.83,0:08:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是老師曾經對我說的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.54,0:08:18.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.88,0:08:20.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔那裡雇用的保鑣之一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.71,0:08:25.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是帶著一只黑狗在車頂上睡覺
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.93,0:08:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都叫他無名氏約翰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.97,0:08:32.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自稱原來是CIA的探員
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.06,0:08:35.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但誰都不知道他的真實背景
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.74,0:08:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想當殺手的話 就得捨棄無聊的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.49,0:08:54.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躊躇不前的傢伙是軟弱的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.50,0:08:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把別人的命當作是垃圾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.25,0:09:00.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那後來他怎樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.89,0:09:14.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某天 很突然地死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.19,0:09:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明如此強悍 卻被流彈擊中了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.61,0:09:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福蘭克和福蘭卡都是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.95,0:09:28.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你們要是死了的話就太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.24,0:09:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我覺得這麼想也不好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.58,0:09:37.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約翰他也許是因此才死的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.54,0:09:41.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.79,0:09:44.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起來並不是會迷茫的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.59,0:09:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和福蘭卡是情侶嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.51,0:09:50.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.81,0:09:57.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她喚醒了行屍走肉的我 要我好好地生活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.81,0:10:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她對我來說就是活下去的動機
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.94,0:10:08.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像柯里斯迪阿諾對你的意義一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.91,0:10:11.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.34,0:10:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想見見叔叔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.85,0:11:25.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是那首曲子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.48,0:11:29.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是柯里斯迪阿諾以前一直演奏的曲子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.69,0:11:32.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道彈鋼琴是在他那裡學會的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.66,0:11:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說是一直在旁邊聽著才學會的 所以只會彈這首
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.74,0:11:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是悲哀啊 明明是他的養父
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.33,0:11:44.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻什麼都沒教會他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.22,0:11:52.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.38,0:11:55.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 帕歐拉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.35,0:11:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬利諾福先生的電話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.89,0:12:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 馬利諾福叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.44,0:12:04.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 卡特麗娜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.27,0:12:09.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經兩個月沒法聯絡到您 我真的很擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.15,0:12:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在羅馬和你見面後
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.19,0:12:15.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被警察追捕 暫時就躲起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.16,0:12:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.58,0:12:22.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說你遇到了危險 能平安無事就太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.91,0:12:24.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然想跟你舊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.00,0:12:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今天是緊急事件
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.00,0:12:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然和以前你說的米蘭派內部紛爭也有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.05,0:12:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但...似乎柯里斯迪阿諾終於失去權力了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.93,0:12:41.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個受到的損傷可是很重大
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.02,0:12:46.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼多軍警同胞被殺 並用武器的提供也被封鎖
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.52,0:12:51.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可別忘了誘拐計劃也是慘烈收場
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.57,0:12:58.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之這半年的事件如果沒有誰負起責任的話可是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.33,0:13:10.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近米蘭派在和政府機關的爭鬥中一直失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.92,0:13:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照這種不利的情況來看 恐怕過不了多久
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.88,0:13:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們也要向當局妥協了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.22,0:13:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹部內部的討論似乎是這麼決定的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.31,0:13:30.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如果今後還想以五共和國派名義繼續行動的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.77,0:13:33.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和柯里斯迪阿諾斷了關係
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.11,0:13:35.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了沒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.53,0:13:38.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.67,0:13:54.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮諾曹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.76,0:13:56.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在寢具裡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.38,0:13:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.93,0:14:03.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙喝酒喝醉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.81,0:14:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天第一次喝酒精類東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.65,0:14:16.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.75,0:14:30.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 要柯里斯迪阿諾背負起責任
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.13,0:14:36.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.47,0:14:42.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔要我在這裡安靜地待段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.10,0:14:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫時先觀望下 但要如何告訴皮諾曹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.31,0:14:49.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.86,0:14:56.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓他不失去權力的可能性還是有的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.65,0:15:02.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他消失的話 米蘭派說不定會和政府妥協
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.41,0:15:04.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那樣的話 對於我們也是不利的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.78,0:15:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.95,0:15:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要炸飛這玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.04,0:15:14.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.00,0:15:21.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在建設墨西哥大橋前為了調查而建造的實驗橋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.84,0:15:26.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這座橋比較小 所以即使用手頭上的炸彈也能解決
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.89,0:15:30.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果成功的話 不管怎樣也會暫時停止建設
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.39,0:15:33.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能回避一下柯里斯迪阿諾的責任
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.31,0:15:37.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 我明白了做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.02,0:15:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就開始準備 明天下午出發
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.70,0:15:45.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福蘭克
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.58,0:15:48.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.25,0:15:58.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個幹部是半年前來過佛羅倫薩的男人?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.92,0:16:01.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 因為皮利亞崔逃稅事件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.17,0:16:08.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米蘭派今早和內務部聯絡 聲稱願意有條件地告訴我們他的具體所在地
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.39,0:16:10.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.22,0:16:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎樣的人物?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.85,0:16:15.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柯里斯迪阿諾．薩博納．洛拉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.65,0:16:20.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為五共和國派鮮有的從中產階級掘起的暴發型幹部
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.65,0:16:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此在米蘭派中也有很多人排斥他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.49,0:16:28.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薩博納．洛拉? 就算是巧合也很諷刺
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.58,0:16:31.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姓可能是自稱也說不定
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.87,0:16:36.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來是個喜歡藝術的男人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.79,0:16:41.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他現在似乎專門負責墨西哥大橋的恐怖活動
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.17,0:16:45.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以出動兄妹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.43,0:16:50.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,許可 同時拘捕米蘭派的柯里斯迪阿諾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.64,0:16:57.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薩博納．洛拉?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.98,0:17:02.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五百年前掌握佛羅倫薩大權的修道士
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.03,0:17:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,施行著神的教導之下的虛幻政治 結果眾叛親離
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.78,0:17:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最終被處刑了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.08,0:17:15.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好怪的頭巾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.00,0:17:20.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.54,0:17:23.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庫拉艾斯 特麗艾拉在嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.01,0:17:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 在的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.22,0:17:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.06,0:17:35.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特麗艾拉 突然有工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.27,0:17:38.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是米蘭嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.27,0:17:42.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.94,0:17:48.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天我要去米蘭 利柯也一起哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.95,0:17:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.03,0:17:54.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉艾塔和貝阿托莉琪去墨西哥那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.41,0:17:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就拜託你看家咯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.91,0:17:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.25,0:18:01.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是米蘭嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.25,0:18:05.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 說要抓住五共和國派的大人物呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.38,0:18:08.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體不要緊了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.63,0:18:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 完全不要緊了 我會加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.93,0:18:17.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 要去破壞橋嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.69,0:18:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果順利的話 今晚就能解決
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.56,0:18:24.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 期待你們的成果
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.15,0:18:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和皮諾曹說話嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.57,0:18:29.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.41,0:18:34.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.78,0:18:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮諾曹 還好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.12,0:18:37.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福蘭卡和福蘭克就拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.08,0:18:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別讓那兩個人死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.46,0:18:45.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.21,0:18:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.63,0:18:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.63,0:18:52.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.76,0:18:53.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要小心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.64,0:18:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.23,0:19:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樣子感覺有點怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.03,0:19:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.40,0:19:15.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 會不會是因為我們修正了計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.79,0:19:21.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我們成功了就沒問題了 別在意了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.83,0:19:22.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.23,0:19:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墨西拿海峽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.65,0:19:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要從陸地過去是完全不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.24,0:19:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警備太嚴密了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.58,0:20:03.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能用船從海上靠近了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.37,0:20:06.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能實驗橋沒有警備
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.42,0:20:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衛星照片上沒看到警備艇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.59,0:20:13.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果現在也是那樣就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.34,0:20:18.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貝爾納爾多 你那邊怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.77,0:20:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺不到特別可疑的空氣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.10,0:20:24.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貝琪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.02,0:20:26.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 貝爾納爾多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.19,0:20:28.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼氣味嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.77,0:20:29.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.44,0:20:33.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 喬澤 今晚帕達尼亞真的會來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.24,0:20:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這樣的警備下 他們也不敢靠近吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.83,0:20:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們先從建設大橋現場大門回來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.37,0:20:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們步行到實驗橋去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.21,0:20:47.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 海莉艾塔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.96,0:20:48.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.77,0:21:07.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.61,0:21:09.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.77,0:21:54.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼的初次工作似乎很順利啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.28,0:21:57.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼把殺人的技術教給他
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.57,0:22:00.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他自己提出的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.62,0:22:02.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他希望幫上你的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.58,0:22:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼有天生的才能
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.08,0:22:10.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天會成為偉大的殺手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.17,0:22:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是吹什麼風啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.96,0:22:18.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了這個年齡也明白了教導別人是件有趣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.01,0:22:24.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...就如同是自己的分身留在這個世界上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.81,0:22:31.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 不行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.15,0:22:40.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也罷 反正只是心血來潮才會收養的孤兒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.53,0:22:45.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心血來潮? 不對啊 老闆也想要個兒子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.24,0:22:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才給他取了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.42,0:22:55.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說到底我也只是個活得比較富裕的小流氓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.38,0:22:57.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒資格養育孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.13,0:23:02.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父愛的表現也是多種多樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.72,0:23:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將他作為部下差遣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.73,0:23:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是把他作為殺人的道具 也是其中一種
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.98,0:23:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一直鼓吹 動了情就會變軟弱 嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.74,0:23:27.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來我也已經老了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.66,0:23:29.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是嫉妒他對你的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.58,0:23:32.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算是其中一種樂趣

Dialogue: -1,0:01:44.00,0:01:48.02,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}堅持著唯一的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.00,0:01:48.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}堅持著唯一的夢想
Dialogue: -1,0:01:47.87,0:01:51.67,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}千難萬苦之中的我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.87,0:01:51.67,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}千難萬苦之中的我
Dialogue: -1,0:01:51.52,0:01:55.56,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}想堅守到底給你看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.52,0:01:55.56,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}想堅守到底給你看
Dialogue: -1,0:01:55.41,0:01:59.37,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}只為那不可替代的人兒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.41,0:01:59.37,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}只為那不可替代的人兒
Dialogue: -1,0:01:59.22,0:02:05.44,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,800)}我切望實現的約定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.22,0:02:05.44,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,800)}我切望實現的約定啊
Dialogue: -1,0:02:06.55,0:02:10.32,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}在這充滿疑問的世界裡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.55,0:02:10.32,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}在這充滿疑問的世界裡
Dialogue: -1,0:02:10.47,0:02:14.02,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}儘管還沒能找尋到答案
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.47,0:02:14.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}儘管還沒能找尋到答案
Dialogue: -1,0:02:14.14,0:02:20.84,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}卻還要一往無前  Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.14,0:02:20.84,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}卻還要一往無前  Why?
Dialogue: -1,0:02:21.25,0:02:24.70,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}宛如夢幻般的現實
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.25,0:02:24.70,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}宛如夢幻般的現實
Dialogue: -1,0:02:25.28,0:02:31.66,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}若能親手改變的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.28,0:02:31.66,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}若能親手改變的話
Dialogue: -1,0:02:31.61,0:02:35.54,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}堅持著唯一的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.61,0:02:35.54,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}堅持著唯一的夢想
Dialogue: -1,0:02:35.39,0:02:39.42,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}千難萬苦之中的我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.39,0:02:39.42,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}千難萬苦之中的我
Dialogue: -1,0:02:39.27,0:02:43.25,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}想堅守到底給你看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.27,0:02:43.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}想堅守到底給你看
Dialogue: -1,0:02:43.00,0:02:46.97,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}只為那不可替代的人兒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.00,0:02:46.97,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}只為那不可替代的人兒
Dialogue: -1,0:02:47.00,0:02:50.86,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}向心潮起伏的胸口宣誓
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.00,0:02:50.86,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}向心潮起伏的胸口宣誓
Dialogue: -1,0:02:50.71,0:02:54.70,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}義無反顧直到油盡燈枯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.71,0:02:54.70,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}義無反顧直到油盡燈枯
Dialogue: -1,0:02:54.55,0:02:56.51,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}正因我艱辛地活著
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.55,0:02:56.51,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}正因我艱辛地活著
Dialogue: -1,0:02:56.46,0:02:58.40,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}所以我能夠感覺到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.46,0:02:58.40,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}所以我能夠感覺到
Dialogue: -1,0:02:58.25,0:03:02.24,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}在那永無止境的愛的包圍中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.25,0:03:02.24,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}在那永無止境的愛的包圍中
Dialogue: -1,0:03:02.09,0:03:10.89,OPch2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\be1\fad(150,300)}我切望實現的約定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.09,0:03:10.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,391)}{\fad(150,300)}我切望實現的約定啊


Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.18,0:23:51.73,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}從那溫暖的雙手中誕生的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.34,0:23:59.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}是一個沒有心靈的人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.23,0:24:03.95,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}未曾有過歡笑
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.30,0:24:08.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}也不曾有過話語
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.59,0:24:17.26,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}多麼希望有一天能夠被人傾聽的這份思念
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.82,0:24:25.38,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}雖然難以化作言語
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.85,0:24:33.52,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,300)}但也會竭盡全力地去傳達
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.00,0:24:57.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(150,10000)}只因深知自己要好好活下去